

CONTACTS

+38 (097) 989-80-12 leonid.yezerskyi@ gmail.com <u>Telegram</u> <u>Linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u> Kyiv, Ukraine

TECH SKILS

- HTML5/CSS3/SASS
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- GIT
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- Next.js
- REST API
- Handlebars
- Webpack
- Node.js
- Express
- Docker
- Figma
- MongoDB
- React Native

SOFT SKILLS

- Determined
- Eager to learn
- Strong adaptation skills
- Team work
- Risk taking

LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian Native
- English Fluent
- Russian Fluent

Leonid Yezerskyi

Junior Full Stack Developer

SUMMARY

I am a full stack developer with one year of commercial experience. I have a solid understanding of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Next.js, Tailwind, TypeScript, Node.js/Express, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Neon DB, Supabase, Strapi, Payload CMS, React Native, Clerk Auth, OpenAI, Paddle, LiqPay. I am committed to continuously learning new technologies and enhancing my IT skills. I like to work for hours and hours and to focus on different tasks. I always say - it is important to challenge yourself, and to enjoy it no matter how difficult it can be. Therefore, I am up for any challenge.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

- <u>CafeTobi</u> [HTML, JS, React, Next.js, Redux Toolkit, Redux-Persist, Axios, Poster, LiqPay] It is a commercial project. A full stack restaurant website where you can view the menu, order food for delivery, pay online. Role: full stack developer (the design and development is all mine).
- <u>Card Real Estate</u> [JS, Next.js, Payload CMS, Neon database, Typescript, Node/Express, Clerk AUTH]

It is a commercial project. A website connected to a Payload CMS and Neon database, with authorization - for real estate agents. Role: full stack developer.

 Letterpal App [JS, Next.js, Tailwind, Strapi CMS, Postgres, Neon database, Typescript, Node, Clerk AUTH, Paddle, OpenAI, TipTap]

It is a commercial project. A website to generate a cover letter in seconds with artificial intelligence. Role: full stack developer. I can show it in the private call.

• Pets, Link [HTML, JS, Vite, React, Redux, CatAPI]

The app for getting to know different breeds of cats in enjoyable way. Pet project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer, Mavens Tech Lab INC (Miami, Florida, United States) 02.2024 - present (part time job)

Merchandiser, "Heinemann Duty Free" (Germany), "Kyiv" International Airport 20.05.2021-24.02.2022

- Ensuring the appropriate range of products in four stores.
- Analytical work with large a volume of information. The number of product names for which I was responsible for is about 1000.

Traveler and writer, self employed

7.10.2016 - 20.12.2019

• I travelled for 3 years and visited 25 countries.

Achievement: I was able to start this trip with 100\$ only.

Editor, chief of "news/capital" department

Newspaper "Gazeta po-ukrainsky", magazine "Kraina", site "gazeta.ua" (Kyiv) 1.04.2010 – 15.04.2016

- Filling publications with relevant interesting

- Filling publications with relevant, interesting and useful information.
- Coordinating the work of journalists in the main office, four regional offices, and freelance correspondents in the biggest cities of Ukraine.
- Editing of materials according to corporate standards.

Achievement: Materials of our department were constantly published on the front page of the newspaper. I developed and managed the news department "capital" from zero.

EDUCATION

• IT School GoIT (Kyiv) - 2022-2023

Fullstack Developer

• Zaporizhzhya National University - 2008-2009

Master of Journalism

• Mykolaiv State University - 2004-2008

Bachelor of Journalism, Publishing and Editing